can make me a little uncomfortable.
最新连载海外影视剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com 仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Alex, you should know
翻译    @少年影视派    油腻希
Adolfo of Venice.
翻译     洗七里    前妻客串赛钱钱
Alan Carpman of Bakersfield.
时间轴   三水
but he stole my hair dye formula.
后期    加森
- Bye, Phil. ?- Bye.
-再见  菲尔  -再见
All right, well, I parked on the street,
好了  我把车停在路旁了
so I'll just meet you at home.
我们回家见吧
- Bye, Claire. - I need to run to the mall.
-再见  克莱尔  -我需要去一趟商场
Would you pick up some steaks from the farmers market for tonight?
你能从农贸市场买些牛排晚上吃吗
Oh, so you did remember it's date night.
所以你还记得今晚是约会之夜
I was a little worried after your response to my Paperless Post.
你没回我的无纸化邀请函  让我还有点担心呢
Oh, come on.
拜托
You know my maybes always turn into will attends.
你知道我说的"或许"最终都是"确定参加"
Okay.
好的
When was the last time that you and I
你和我上一次
cooked a romantic dinner together?
一起准备浪漫晚餐是什么时候了
We did it last week.
我们上周才弄过啊
I'm not talking about sprinkling hot dog slices on a DiGiorno's.
我说的可不是简单地把热狗片撒在披萨上
You couldn't bring my car before I got in trouble?
你就不能在我挨说之前把车开来吗
Thank you.
谢谢
I've been secretly moonlighting as an online food blogger,
我一直悄悄在网上当美食博主
"Foodie in a Hoodie"
账号叫"帽衫美食家"
it rhymes on the page.
是一个押韵的名字
I've quickly developed a huge following,
我很快就收获了一大批粉丝
and The Prescott is home to the city's hottest restaurant,
普雷斯科综合生活馆有着全市最火的餐厅
called Pardon.
叫"什么餐厅"
Hello.
你好
Ah, good day, sir.
您好  先生
Forgive me. I'm new here.
请原谅  我是新来的
Still getting to know each of the tenants.
我还在努力认识这里所有的住户
I'm your concierge, Higgins.
我是这里的管理员希金斯
You look so familiar. Have we met?
你看着好眼熟啊  我们以前见过吗
'Fraid not, no.
恐怕没有
I do get that a lot, though.
不过经常有人这么说
I have an everyman face and body.
我长着一张大众脸  大众身材
They're rising.
机器人崛起了
Ah, yes, Finley.
没错  芬利
Patrols the building for non-residents
它负责巡查大楼  搜出非住户
using a motion sensor and face scanner.
全靠运动感应器和面部扫描仪
Useful, yes, but does he have that uniquely human ability
确实非常有用  但它拥有独特的人类本事
to anticipate a person's every need?
能提前预料到人的每一项需求吗
Coconut water?
喝椰子水吗
I didn't even know I wanted this!
我都没意识到我想喝水呢
Finley, away!
芬利  走开
Anything else I can help you with, sir?
还有什么能帮到您的吗  先生
No. I'm just headed down to the restaurant.
没了  我直接去餐厅
Pardon?
什么
Your...in-house eatery.
你们的  内部食堂
You know -- uh, waiters, cutlery, daily specials.
就是  服务生  餐具  每日特色菜
I think it's called Pardon.
好像是叫"什么餐厅"
- Of course. My mistake. - It's all right.
-当然了  我的错  -没事
Right this way.
请这边走
Avoiding the security robot would be tricky,
要躲避安保机器人会很棘手
but Finley had a weakness --
但芬利有个弱点
he can only detect people if they're moving.
它只能侦测到在移动的人
And it was worth the risk --
那值得冒险啊
Pardon claimed to have the world's best beef slider,
"什么餐厅"的小汉堡号称是全世界最美味的
and my -- my followers are dying for a review.
我的粉丝全都超想看到我的点评
Well, all but one.
除了一个人
I have a troll.
我有个黑子
Screen name "Close to Utlaw," Wherever that is.
网名叫"厨巨王走"  鬼知道那是什么
We recently got into a -- a heated comment war.
我们最近在评论里发生了撕逼大战
Insults were hurled, mothers disparaged.
脏话乱飚  操爹骂娘
Who knew the Internet could be so negative?
谁能想到网络这么负能量呢
Table for one. I live here.
一人位  我住这里
Something just opened up.
刚出来个空桌
Great, lead the way. I live here.
好极了  带路吧  我住这里
Hi. Uh, I'm new here.
嗨  我初来乍到
Could you lead me to the screening room?
你能领我去放映室吗
I should think so.
我觉得可以吧
At the butler academy, I led my class in leading.
在管家学院  我在领路方面可是全班第一名
This way.
这边请
Recently, I got a special edition Blu-ray
最近  我搞到了有史以来
of the best movie ever made, "Lawrence of Arabia."
最伟大的电影《阿拉伯的劳伦斯》的蓝光盘
Word is, The Prescott has
据传  普雷斯科综合生活馆
a state-of-the-art screening room with surround sound.
拥有最顶尖的放映室  带环绕声
Know what it doesn't have?
知道它没有什么吗
Manny.
曼尼
Hello! I would've gone with a tracking shot there.
拜托  我觉得这里用推拉镜头才更合适吧
I sure hope he finds a plot out there in that desert.
希望他在沙漠里能找到精彩情节
Behold, our famous candy wall.
看吧  我们出名的糖果墙
Hey, Sugar Babies.
嘿  甜心宝宝
Yes, honey buns?
什么事  糖心贝贝
?No, Sugar Babies. The greatest movie candy of all time.
不  甜心宝宝是有史以来最适合看电影时吃的糖
A thousand apologies.
万分抱歉
I will track some down for you straight away.
我马上去给您弄一些来
- You wouldn't mind? - Mind? Please.
-你不介意吗  -介意什么  拜托
There is no greater joy
我最大的乐趣
than fetching something I've never heard of
就是去搞到一些我从未听过的东西
for someone I've only just met.
给一个我刚认识的人
May I help you with something?
请问有什么需要帮忙的吗
No, I'm just -- I'm waiting for someone.
不用  我只是在等人而已
And his name is David Beckham.
那个人叫大卫・贝克汉姆
Resident at The Prescott.
他就住在普雷斯科综合生活馆
Okay, Mitchell hates it when I do this,
米奇很讨厌我做这种事
but every time I meet a celebrity,
但我每次遇见名人
I ask them to record my outgoing message.
我都拜托他们帮我录来电语音应答
My current one is from when I saw Snoop Dogg at a bank.
我现在用的是我在银行遇到史诺普・道格时录的
Sorry I missed you. As you can see --
抱歉我没看见你  如你所见
I'm busy!
老子在忙
And sometimes things can --
有时事情会...
Get away from me!
离老子远点
Please leave a message, including your phone number,
请留言  并留下你的电话号码
just for -- ?Security!
那是为了...保安[安全着想]
Hey, sweetie, what's up? I'm -- I'm kind of busy.
宝贝  什么事  我这会儿有点忙
Cam, I'm hurt. It's my leg.
小卡  我受伤了  是我的腿
What?
什么
I slipped in the food court,
我在美食街滑倒了
and I'm all sticky and tweens are laughing at me.
现在全身都粘粘的  而且还被十岁小屁孩嘲笑
You have to come pick me up.
你一定要来接我
Well, that sounds awful, but --
听起来好惨  但是
Isn't -- Isn't Claire closer?
克莱尔不是离你更近吗
Well, you're at the farmers market right down the street.
可你就在街尾的农贸市场啊
Okay, fine. I'm on my way.
行吧  我这就来
Aww, you're the best.
老公你最好啦
I was not gonna let Cam ruin my chance
我绝不能让小卡毁了我当面感谢
to thank my wallpaper, Victoria Beckham, one-on-one.
我的壁纸  维多利亚・贝克汉姆的机会
Okay, so, it was 1997.
当时是1997年
I was in Detroit for a Spice Girls concert with my girlfriend.
我和女朋友在底特律看辣妹合唱团演唱会
I was going to propose to her,
我本来打算向她求婚的
had the ring in my pocket and everything,
戒指什么的都准备好了
when from the stage, Posh looked right at me and said,
结果时髦辣妹从台上径直看向我  并说道
"Be true to yourself, Mitchell!"
"要直面真正的你  米奇尔"
Okay, you know, she might've said "Michigan,"
好吧  她说的可能是"密歇根"
but she was looking right at me!
但她当时目光正对着我
She inspired me to come out that night.
那一晚我受到她的鼓舞而出柜
I had that diamond reset as an anklet charm,
我把那颗钻石挂到脚链上当幸运符
and I was off to the races.
接下来我就夜夜笙歌了
What kind of gym bag is that, anyway?
那到底是哪门子的奇葩健身袋啊
It's a satchel, you ignorant sneeze.
这是挎包  你个无知白痴
You have been so unpleasant lately.
你最近好暴躁好讨厌
On a definitely related note,
与他这态度绝对有关的就是
Manny hasn't gotten any action in months.
曼尼有好几个月没做过床上"运动"了
Well, other than whatever gave him carpal tunnel.
好吧  除了害他得腕管综合征的运动外
Luckily, The Prescott has an '80s aerobi-cise class,
幸好普雷斯科综合生活馆有80年代有氧健身操课程
which will be full of single older ladies.
现场会有很多单身熟女
Women hit a sweet spot right after 40
女人一过40岁就到达一个黄金交叉点
where they still look great
那时她们外表仍然美丽
but their standards have lowered.
但对男人的要求大大降低
You're in pretty good shape for someone who's...
你身材保持得不错啊  毕竟你已经...
42? 43?
42岁  43岁了
I'm 38.
我才38
Bye.
再见
Higgins.
希金斯
Oh, Mr. Beckham. Apologies.
贝克汉姆先生  抱歉
Blind as a bat without these bad boys.
我没戴眼镜时就跟蝙蝠一样眼瞎
So, myself and Courteney are expecting a bowling instructor.
我和柯特妮跟保龄球教练约好了
Would you have him meet us
麻烦你叫他
downstairs at the bowling alley, please?
到楼下的保龄球馆找我们  好吗
You and Ms. Cox getting an edge
你和考克斯女士要为
for this weekend's celebrity bowl-a-thon?
周末的名人马拉松保龄球赛大练身手吗
Oh, we'll need it.
我们绝对需要练习
You should've seen the way he bowled last year.
你没看到去年比赛他打得有多烂
I mean, it is to raise money for charity.
可那比赛只是要为慈善筹款啊
Yeah, a dollar for each of the 18 pins that you knocked down.
没错  你总共击倒的18个瓶募到18块钱呢
Thanks to you, Doctors Without Borders
多亏了你  无国界医生们
are now Doctors Without Malaria Pills.
现在成了无痢疾药医生
A bit harsh.
有点毒
Did you see the two friends in the back?
你看到后面那两位女士了吗
The blond one liked me, and the brunette kept staring at you.
金发那个喜欢我  褐发那个一直盯着你看
Can you blame her?
你能怪她吗
No one moves to "Caribbean Queen" Like me.
我跳《加勒比海女王》的舞步  无人能及
Ah, just who I was told to be on the lookout for.
我正要找你们
A certain couple have asked
有两个人叫你们
that you meet them in the bowling alley.
去保龄球馆找他们
Was it a blonde and a brunette?
是不是一位金发  一位棕发的
Indeed, and they seemed eager to get rolling.
没错  而且他们等不及要"开滚"了
Bowling alley?
保龄球馆
These girls are freaky.
这些妹子口味真重
Hair salon?
美发沙龙在哪
- Just off the courtyard to your right. - Thank you.
-穿过院子  在您右手边  -谢谢
I've always wanted to dye my hair dark.
我一直想把头发染成深色
But there's only one colorist I would trust to do it --
但我放心委以重任的染发师只有一位
Adolfo of Venice.
威尼斯的阿道夫
Gloria's sworn enemy.
歌洛莉亚的死对头
I just have to sneak back in and do it without her knowing.
我得偷偷绕回来染发  不让她知道
Hi, Mom.
妈妈好啊
Hi, Alex. Hey, honey.
艾丽克斯  宝贝
So, how's the project going?
你的项目进展如何
I'm never gonna make this deadline.
我肯定赶不上最后期限了
Oh, yeah, no, that -- that -- that's tough...
不会吧  好惨哦
I'm sorry -- sorry to hear that.
听到你这么说我很难过
Work is so stressful.
工作真是让我压力山大
Yeah, got to go, love you! Bye!
我得挂了  爱你哦  再见
The pool?
泳池在哪
Just hop on the elevator
您进电梯
and press the big button marked "Pool."
按下写着"泳池"的大按键就能到达
I am known as the fearless one of the family.
众人皆知我是这个家里最大胆无畏的
So, when Claire gave us all free passes
所以克莱尔给我们下周
for the Fun Town Water Park next week,
快乐镇水上乐园的免费票后
I couldn't admit that I am afraid of slides.
我不敢承认我怕滑滑梯
They go so fast, I feel like I'm going to fly off.
水上滑梯速度好快  我觉得自己都要飞出去了
I just need to try it once and I am going to be fine.
我需要先滑一次  到时我就不怕了
I cannot do it!
我做不到
Hey, no backsies!
不准反悔哦
Okay, here I go!
好吧  我滑了
You should have let me do backsies!
你应该让我反悔的
Resident ID access -- hair salon.
住户已进入  美发沙龙
What? Who's using my code?!
什么  谁偷用了我的密码
You a-look like that a-actress...
你看起来就像那个女演员
Audrey Hepburn.
奥黛丽・赫本
This is Phil Dunphy. Leave a message.
我是菲尔・邓菲  请留言
Phil, I have a little surprise for you later.
菲尔  我晚点有个惊喜送给你
Let's just say I know how much you love brunettes.
这么说吧  我知道你有多喜欢褐发美女
- Here's a menu for you. ?- Thank you.
-菜单给您  -谢谢
And for my followers...
先拍张照片
an Instagram tease.
吊吊我粉丝们的胃口
Your Sugar Babies, sir.
您的甜心宝宝  先生
I hope it wasn't too much trouble.
希望没让你太费心
On the contrary.
恰恰相反
There was a Mexican birthday celebration
街对面的公园里正在举办
taking place in the park across the street.
墨西哥生日庆祝会
I waited for the crack of the pinata,
我等他们敲破塞满糖果的皮纳塔后
mixed in seamlessly with the children,
就无耻地混进小孩子中间
and pounced.
伺机猛抢糖果
He's here?!
他也在这吗
Some moron food blogger took a shot
一个白痴美食博主攻击
at one of my favorite spots.
我最喜欢的其中一家餐厅
So I go after him using my screen name, "Closet Outlaw."
于是我用艺名"橱柜狂徒"去网上骂他
It escalates, and he turns his army of followers against me.
骂战升级  他唆使他一大票粉丝来围攻我
As I wrote in my last comment --
我就在最后一条评论里写道
"Let's see how well my fist pairs with your face."
"看看是我的拳头硬  还是你的脸硬"
The bowling alley?!
保龄球馆
Alex is here?!
艾丽克斯在这
If she sees us, she'll throw us out.
假如她看到我们  会赶我们出去的
Excuse me.
不好意思
If that blonde and brunette come by,
要是金发和棕发那两位来了
could you tell them there's a new meet-up spot?
你能不能告诉他们碰面地点换了
The hot tubs on the rooftop.
换成顶楼的按摩浴缸
Of course, warm things up a bit before your workout.
当然  锻炼前先热身
If there's nothing else, I need to make sure
假如您没有其他需求  我得继续检查
these balls are marked with their correct weights.
确保保龄球的重量没有标错
Size 10 for him
给他10号的鞋
and anything with a steel toe for me.
给我一双有钢头的
Someone drops his ball a lot.
某人总是出纰漏[掉球]
There has been a change of plan.
计划有变
Your bowling instructor would now like you to meet him
你们的保龄球教练说在顶楼碰面
in the hot tubs for a warmup first.
要在按摩浴缸里热身
- Meet you up there? - ?Yep.
-楼上见吧  -好
If you're calling the charity for a new partner,
假如你想打给慈善机构换搭档
it's not gonna work.
那是行不通的
They already made the posters.
他们已经做好海报了
- Ready to order? - ?Very.
-可以点餐了吗  -迫不及待
I came to this restaurant for one thing and one thing only.
我来这间餐厅只想点一样菜品
And that thing is...?
是什么菜
Sorry. Uh, one of your world fa--
抱歉  来一份你们世上最肥...
One of our world's fattest hot dogs coming up.
世上最肥的热狗  这就来
No! The-the slider.
不  是肥美小汉堡
And how would you like it?
肉饼要几分熟
Me...
我
- Yes, you, sir. ?- ...dium rare.
-是的  您  先生  -要三分熟
And can you have it delivered to the pool, please?
能请你送到泳池来吗
Of course.
当然
Okay, that slider goes to the pool,
那份小汉堡送到泳池
and it looks like we need one for Mr. Beckham to the roof.
还有一份贝克汉姆先生的送到顶楼
You seen a guy in a black hoodie?
你见到过穿黑帽衫的家伙吗
- Just left. - ?Thanks.
-他刚走  -谢了
Oh, I'll be back.
我去去就回
I'm dying to try one of your world's fattest hot dogs.
我迫不及待想尝尝你们世上最肥的热狗
Hey, you here at the mall?
你到商场了吗
No, not yet. Why are you breathing so hard?
还没  你怎么喘得这么厉害
Oh, um, a bunch of kids were vaping next to me,
一群孩子在我旁边抽电子烟
and I had to army-crawl into a-a candle store.
我不得不伏地爬到香薰店里
Yeah. Is there anything you want while I'm here?
我来都来了  你想买什么吗
Can I tell you what I want, what I really, really want?
我能告诉你我"真正真正想要的"吗
You're watching me right now, aren't you?
你正在看着我对吗
Cam, okay, look.
小卡  好吧
I was hoping I'd run into Posh
我只是希望能在健身房
here at the gym for a private moment, okay?
遇到时髦辣妹聊上两句  好吗
Look, we're both after the Beckhams.
我们都希望遇到贝克汉姆夫妇
Let's come up with a plan together --
我们一起制定一个计划
meet me at the swim-up bar.
在泳池酒吧等我
There's a swim-up bar?!
他们还有泳池酒吧
I know, we should be living here
就是说  我们才该住在这里
and Alex should be living in our stupid house.
艾丽克斯该住在我们的破房子里
Higgins, I need you!
希金斯  我需要你
Where are you?!
你在哪
A spot of bother, I see?
您似乎遇到小麻烦了
I can't do it!
我做不到
Oh, of course you can.
您当然可以
I'll just crawl in front of you
我爬到您身前
so you can grab me around the waist.
您就可以抓住我的腰
I apologize in advance for any giggling.
要是我笑出声了提前向您道歉
I'm cursed with the tickle gene.
我这人天生很怕痒
What's going on?
出什么事了
Someone's stuck on the slide.
有人卡在滑梯上了
She tried to climb back down, but --
她想爬回去  但是
- No backsies, I get it. - Yeah.
-滑梯不许反悔[倒退]  我懂  -是啊
Oh, oh, oh! That's for me.
那是我的
Thank you.
谢谢
- But it goes too fast! - Oh, no, don't worry.
-可是速度太快了  -不  别担心
I shall vary the flex of my buttocks to control our speed.
我将不断收缩臀部来控制我们的速度
We should be --
我们会
No!
不
My deepest apologies!
请接受我最诚挚的歉意
Okay.
好吧
Noooo!!
不
That one's sorted.
麻烦解决
I need some sparkling water sent up to the hot tub cabanas.
送一些气泡水到按摩浴缸帐篷
Can't say for whom,
不能说是给谁的
but let's include a glass of champagne
但附带一杯香槟
in case his posh wife joins him.
以防他的"时髦"妻子一会儿也来
Easy.
小心
Come on!
有没有搞错
Higgins!
希金斯
Um, listen...
听我说
I need your help getting my hands on the slider.
我需要你帮我弄来那个小汉堡[滑水者]
The slider?
滑水者吗
Oh, of course.
当然
Quite a looker, that one.
看着就诱人
Well, that's the problem -- so far,
问题就在这  目前为止
I've only been able to look and not taste.
我只能看  还没尝到
Say no more. I shall find a way to deliver the slider to you.
无需多言  我会想办法将滑水者送来
Great! Um, is there somewhere private
太好了  有没有什么隐蔽些的地方
where I could enjoy the slider alone?
能让我单独享用它
Might I suggest one of our rooftop hot tubs
我建议您去我们顶楼的按摩浴缸
overlooking the city?
能眺望都市
Perfect, I'll wait there.
完美  我在那等着
And I'll-I'll need a bib -- I can make a mess.
我还需要一个围嘴  我总搞得满身污渍
Still crisp.
还很脆
He's close.
他没走远
How'd I get back here?
我怎么又到这来了
Ah, Posh.
时髦辣妹
Thank you.
多谢
Your husband has asked that you meet him
您丈夫叫您去露台碰面
up in one of the rooftop hot tubs for some champagne.
一起在按摩浴缸里喝香槟
Phil.
菲尔
Higgins! The slides aren't the enemy.
希金斯  真正的敌人不是滑梯
Fear is.
而是恐惧
It's always a thrill to see one of my residents grow.
见到我们的住客成长总是如此激动人心
By the way, a certain mystery man
顺带一提  某位神秘的先生
has spotted you around the building
在楼内注意到了您的存在
and has requested your presence on the roof.
他希望您能去顶楼一聚
Jay's finally doing something romantic!
杰总算知道搞浪漫了
Just when I thought he was a clueless grouch.
我还以为他只是个不解风情的糟老头
How many lobbies does this place have?!
这地方有几个大堂啊
Excuse me. Where can I find a bathing suit?
打扰一下  哪里能买到泳衣
Oh, there are complimentary suits in all of the cabanas.
所有帐篷里都有附赠的泳衣
?Worry not, I boil them myself nightly.
别担心  我每晚亲自高温消毒
Let's see a robot do that.
机器人有这本事吗
Hi, Higgins. We have a bit of an unusual request.
希金斯  我们有个不寻常的小请求
Now, we know you need to be discreet, but...
我们知道你必须谨言慎行  不过
we are hoping to have a rendezvous
我们希望能和某位杰出的英国人
with a certain distinguished Brit.
来一场"不期而遇"
Consider it arranged.
我会为二位安排
- Okay. - ?Okay.
-好的  -好的
Still no sign of the ladies.
还是没看到女士们的踪迹
Maybe they're in a different cabana.
或许她们是在另一个帐篷里
Mine's here.
我的到了
Let's wait for the blonde.
陪我等金发妹吧
I only know how to do this with even numbers.
我只有在成双成对的时候才玩得开
Hello, Mr. Robot!
机器人先生
Can you tell me where to go for my romantic surprise?
能告诉我我的浪漫惊喜在哪里吗
Gloria?!
歌洛莉亚
Now mine's here, but yours is gone.
现在我的到了  但你的走了
Now they're both gone!
现在两个都跑了
They'll be back.
她们会回来的
Maybe one of them had a nanny emergency.
或许其中一个保姆出了问题
Let's wait for them in there.
去里面等她们吧
Slider?
小汉堡[滑水者]
Arriving shortly. Cabana 3.
很快就到  请进3号帐篷等
Thank you.
谢谢
Here we are, then.
那事不宜迟  我们开始吧
Higgins, what are you doing?!
希金斯  你在干什么
Oh, role play.
要玩角色扮演啊
I know I am but a lowly stable boy,
我知道我只是个低贱的马夫
unwanted in the master's quarters, but --
不允许进入主人们的住宿区域
Perhaps you'd like to teach me a lesson?
但或许你们会想要好好"教训"我呢
Just stay away from the face.
别伤到脸就行
Uh, obviously there's been some sort of misunderstanding.
我们之间很明显有一些误会
Yeah, do we look like the kind of people
我们看起来像是那种
that would be into some sort of weird role play
会喜欢跟别人玩奇怪角色扮演
involving a stable boy?
而且是带马夫情节的人吗
I'm assuming he's been naughty
我想他非常不乖
and would do anything to keep his job.
会愿意做任何事来保住自己的工作吧
Cam -- Cam?
小卡  小卡
In my defense, I do get this request quite often.
为自己辩护一下  我其实很常接到这种要求
Particularly around the holidays.
尤其是在圣诞节前后
Actually, um...
其实呢...
we were hoping to meet a certain celebrity couple.
我们很希望能跟某一对明星夫妇见面
Yeah. ?Say no more.
无需多言
I make no promises, but let me just
我不能做任何保证  但请两位稍等
wriggle back into my shorts and make some inquiries.
等我穿好裤子  出浴缸尽力安排一下
Ah, wonderful timing!
来得真巧
Please step into Cabana 3 -- your mystery man awaits.
请移驾3号帐篷  您的神秘男士正在等候
Hi.
你好啊
I know that you and I aren't supposed to be here,
我知道我们不应该偷偷在这里见面
but after today,
但经过我今天的经历
I am tired of living a life of fear.
我不想再被恐惧控制生活
Was Gloria Claire's brunette surprise?
歌洛莉亚是克莱尔为我准备的棕发惊喜吗
It all started when Claire gave me a free pass to Fun Town.
起因是克莱尔送了我"乐园"的入场券
I thought, just try it today.
我就想  那今天来试试看
Take a ride, see how it feels.
放胆去"玩"  看看感觉如何
Oh. I never noticed how sexy your feet are.
我以前都没发现你的脚那么性感啊
Thank you, but this isn't happening, Gloria! ?
谢谢夸奖  但我们真的不可以  歌洛莉亚
Oh, there you are. Sorry we missed you at the bowling alley.
你们在这里啊  抱歉我们晚到保龄球场了
She looked different with a headband on.
她绑头带时跟现在看起来不太一样啊
Warming up in a hot tub first --
先在按摩浴缸里暖身
unconventional, but, hey, anything to loosen up Becks.
不是寻常套路  但只要能让小贝放松就行
Did we meet a Becky?
我们有认识叫贝姬的吗
Maybe. There were so many of them.
或许吧  当时那么多女人
So, how old is this Becks?
所以小贝是几岁了来着
44.
44岁
It's on.
好戏上场啦
Oh, there you are.
你们在这里啊
Wait... you're Becks?
等等  你是小贝吗
Yep, and I'm eager to learn.
是啊  我也十分有心想学
A warning -- my form is clumsy, but I'm great on my feet.
警告一下  我身材比较走形了  但我的腿功还是一流
Okay, who gets the dude?
好吧  男的谁来
This never happened.
这件事从未发生过
Fine, I'll take him.
行吧  我来处理他
But we're just gonna hang out and see where it goes.
但我跟他就只是先熟悉一下再看情况啊
Pardon the interruption.
抱歉打扰了
It looks like you're finished with the slider?
看来您已享用完滑水者[小汉堡]啦
I am, and can I be honest? I prefer bigger buns.
是啊  我能说句实话吗  我喜欢面包[屁股]大点
It's wonderful to just talk like men sometimes, isn't it?
偶尔能这样男人与男人间聊天  感觉很不错吧
It is.
是啊
Jay, what are you doing here?
杰  你怎么来了
I've spent the whole day looking for that miserable --
我花了一天的时间在找一个王八...
You're the Foodie in a Who-dy?!
你就是那个毛衫美食家吗
W-Why would you say that?
你为何会这么认为呢
Ketchup!
番茄酱
I'm trying, but I'm lost!
我很努力了  但真的没听懂你的话
You insulted my mother!
你侮辱了我妈
Oh, my God. You're Close to Utlaw?!
天啊  你是厨巨王走吗
It's Closet Outlaw!
是橱柜狂徒
Jay, I don't blame you for being mad.
杰  你生气我不怪你
I-I turned my legions of fans against you, and, uh...
我让我的粉丝大军去喷了你  还有...
it's Foodie in a Hoodie, by -- by the way.
其实是叫帽衫美食家啦
But you got a bigger problem at home that I just heard about,
但我刚听说你家有个比这个严重多了的问题啊
and I think I can help you with it.
我觉得我能帮到你
- Claire? - ?Oh! Gloria.
-克莱尔  -歌洛莉亚
I can't believe you recognized me.
真不敢相信你能认出我
I'm so sorry about my hair.
我的头发真是很对不起了
I'm so glad that we can finally talk about it.
我很高兴我们终于可以聊这件事了
Grow it out, let yourself be a girl.
你就放心让它长吧  让你自己当个女孩
Okay, final set of instructions
好的  最后的安排
on a day that will no doubt be a memorable chapter
今天的一切绝对会是我将要出版的回忆录
in my forthcoming memoir, "You Rang?"
《有何能效劳》中  十分精彩的篇章
You, Cabana 2.
您  去2号帐篷
You, Cabana 3.
您  去3号帐篷
You are romantic.
你真浪漫
Honey, if you don't like my hair, I can change it.
亲爱的  如果你不喜欢我的头发  我可以改掉
What? I love it.
什么  我很喜欢啊
Maybe next week I can arrange
或许下周我可以给你安排
a little rendezvous with a redhead.
与红发女郎的一场约会
O-Okay.
好的
I'm glad we cleared that up.
消除刚才的误会真是太好了
I can't wait for my bowling lesson with you.
我真是等不及要跟你上保龄球课了
Oh, my God.
天啊
Foot-y in a Hoodie was here today.
帽衫美食家今天来过这里呢
Ah, you're great.
你真是太棒了
When does Posh get here?
时髦辣妹什么时候来呢
And I apologize for being late.
很抱歉迟到了
You know, I-I left a message.
我其实有给你语音信箱留言呢
I'm sorry I missed your call.
抱歉错过了你的电话
Can you say that one more time?
你能再说一次这句子吗
So, I got a few incidental charges from yesterday.
我收到了昨天的杂项费用账单
Two hundred dollars for sugar babie procurement.
200块钱的甜心宝宝购入费
Sorry.
抱歉
Eight sliders and one coconut water?
还有8个小汉堡以及1瓶椰子水
He charged me for that?
那瓶水他也收我钱啊
Three hundred dollars for a slide rescue.
300块钱的滑水道救援费
Forty dollars fine for the non-wiping of stationary bike.
40块钱的使用健身单车后未清洁的罚款
I barely sweat.
我都没怎么流汗啊
You are sweating right now.
你现在就满头汗了吧
A hundred and fifty dollars fine for the non-return of legwarmers.
150元的护腿未还罚款
And eight one hundred dollar west world entry fees?
8张100块钱的西部世界门票
Oh my God! We left Cam there.
天啊  我们把小卡忘在那里了
Oh no!
糟了